vegasview.com 2017-06-06

# Prestige Cruises

| 

| New Cruise Search  
---  
Select a Destination:  
Sailing Month: | Nights:  
|   
Select a Cruise Line:  
Select a Ship:  
Select a Departure Port:  

**Pay With Points**

**American Express Membership Rewards® Program**  
If you are an American Express Cardmember enrolled in the American Express Membership Rewards® Pay with Points program, you are now invited to use your points to pay for your next cruise or vacation! American Express Membership Rewards® Points are part of American Express' loyalty program, which enables you to earn points when you use your American Express Card. Now, those points can add up to big savings on your next cruise - and can even pay for the entire vacation!

In Order to Redeem Your Points Call 1-800-758-5693

Enter Your Email  
Address & Receive  
Exclusive Deals & Discounts

At Prestige Travel & Cruises, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized travel experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**

  * When you book your cruise or vacation package we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your reservation request and to notify you of your reservation status.
  * When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.
  * We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web site, new services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable.

**Does Prestige Travel & Cruises protect customer information?**  
All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

**What about "cookies"?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide special website features. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our site.

**Will Prestige Travel & Cruises disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
Prestige Travel & Cruises does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Also, Prestige Travel & Cruises may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**In Summary**  
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on to enhance your overall travel experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Prestige Travel & Cruises. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
